.
.
Where's Heavenly Star?
أين النجم السماوي؟
Always chasing Haichuan Star,
دائما مطاردة Haichuan Star ،
when Heavenly Saint Star gets closer?
عندما يقترب نجم السماء السماوية؟
Haichuaxing will stay away from us.
Haichuaxing سيبقى بعيدا عنا.
But as long as Heavenly Saint Star approaches faster than Haichuan Star,
ولكن ما دامت نجمة السماء السماوية تقترب أسرع من نجمة هايشوان ،
they will be together.
سيكونون معا.
Like,
يحب،
you and me.
أنت وأنا.
I don't think so.
أنا لا أعتقد ذلك.
These two stars collided.
اصطدم هذان النجمان.
That's a disaster.
هذه كارثة.
Ouyang Yuchuan,
أويانغ يوتشوان ،
Yes.
نعم.
Tell me about your mother.
أخبرني عن والدتك.
They love each other,
هم يحبون بعضهم البعض،
Because my grandpa didn't agree.
لأن جدي لم يوافق.
So we split up.
لذلك نحن انفصلنا.
Don't you want to know the truth?
ألا تريد أن تعرف الحقيقة؟
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Auntie probably doesn't want to leave your father.
ربما لا تريد العمة أن تترك والدك.
Like me,
مثلي،
she will leave one day.
سوف تغادر ذات يوم.
If I disappear,
إذا اختفت ،
what will you do?
ماذا ستفعل؟
I don't know what's going on
أنا لا أعرف ما يحدث
between you and my biological mother?
بينك وبين أمي البيولوجية؟
I don't think you'll leave me like her.
لا أعتقد أنك ستتركني مثلها.
You always said that I was set up,
قلت دائمًا إنني مهيأ ،
that I exist because of you.
أني موجود بسببك.
Silly girl,
فتاة سخيفة،
forget it.
انسى ذلك.
Go back to sleep.
إرجع إلى النوم.
Aunt Ouyang should have gotten Stallone's heart,
كان يجب على العمة أويانج أن تحصل على قلب ستالون ،
so she had no choice but to go back to her own world,
لذلك لم يكن لديها خيار سوى العودة إلى عالمها الخاص ،
I think I already know what Stallone's heart is.
أعتقد أنني أعرف بالفعل ما هو قلب ستالون.
Should I keep looking?
هل يجب أن أستمر في البحث؟
Only you deserve my exclusive love.
أنت فقط تستحق حبي الحصري.
Su Shengnan,
سو شنغنان ،
what are you thinking?
بماذا تفكر؟
You and Ouyang Yuchuan are from two different worlds,
أنت وأويانغ يوتشوان من عالمين مختلفين ،
not to mention,
ناهيك عن،
You're about to leave this world.
أنت على وشك مغادرة هذا العالم.
When it is broken, it will be broken,
عندما ينكسر ، سوف ينكسر ،
leaving no future trouble.
لا تترك أي مشاكل في المستقبل.
I can't give Ouyang Yuchuan any more hope.
لا يمكنني إعطاء المزيد من الأمل لـ Ouyang Yuchuan.
Knock,
طرق،
knock, bunny,
طرق ، أرنب ،
Good morning.
صباح الخير.
Get up. If you don't get up,
استيقظ.  إذا لم تستيقظ ،
I'm coming in.
أنا قادم.
Bunny,
الأرنب
didn't we agree to go to work together?
الم نوافق على الذهاب للعمل معا؟
you left in a hurry this morning,
غادرت على عجل هذا الصباح ،
I didn't eat breakfast.
لم أتناول الفطور.
This is a bento I made
هذا هو بنتو الذي صنعته
especially for you.
خصيصا لك.
No, thanks.
ًلا شكرا.
I made it myself.
صنعته بنفسي.
I've been studying for a long time.
لقد كنت أدرس لفترة طويلة.
Have a taste.
تذوق.
Ouyang Yuchuan,
أويانغ يوتشوان ،
I have other things to do.
لدي أشياء أخرى للقيام به.
It's delicious.
إنه لذيذ.
Brother Feng,
الأخ فنغ ،
why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Whenever I'm in a bad mood,
عندما أكون في مزاج سيء ،
I come here
اتيت الى هنا
to see the sea,
لرؤية البحر
And then shout a few times,
ثم أصرخ عدة مرات ،
why is Shengnan in a bad mood?
لماذا Shengnan في مزاج سيء؟
Yes.
نعم.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
Sometimes,
أحيانا،
I think we are quite alike.
أعتقد أننا متشابهون تمامًا.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
I can take this opportunity,
يمكنني أن أغتنم هذه الفرصة ،
I apologize to you on behalf of my sister.
أعتذر لك نيابة عن أختي.
It's all in the past.
كل شيء في الماضي.
No need to apologize.
لا داعي للإعتذار.
Leng Yan's current personality and temper,
شخصية لينج يان الحالية ومزاجها ،
in fact, are all my fault.
في الواقع ، كلها خطأي.
When we were little,
عندما كنا صغارا ،
our parents passed away.
توفي والدانا.
As the eldest brother of the family,
بصفتي الأخ الأكبر للعائلة ،
I have to take care of her.
يجب أن أعتني بها.
It was because of my love,
كان بسبب حبي
that she became unreasonable.
أنها أصبحت غير معقولة.
You almost got stung by wasps.
لقد كادت أن تلدغ من الدبابير.
And Ouyang Yuchuan's face
ووجه اويانغ يوتشوان
got swollen.
تورم.
Mr. Ouyang,
السيد أويانغ ،
he doesn't know if I'm in the room,
لا يعرف ما إذا كنت في الغرفة ،
So he rushed inside with his life.
لذلك اندفع إلى الداخل بحياته.
Do you think he's stupid?
هل تعتقد أنه غبي؟
Isn't he worried about you?
ألا يقلق عليك؟
I don't need him to worry.
لا داعي للقلق.
I have nothing to do with him.
لا علاقة لي به.
I just want to
أريد فقط
get a part-time job in this business school,
الحصول على وظيفة بدوام جزئي في كلية إدارة الأعمال هذه ،
That's why I got close to him.
لهذا السبب اقتربت منه.
Sir,
سيد،
what Miss Su said may not be what she meant.
ما قالته الآنسة سو قد لا يكون ما قصدته.
Uncle Wang,
العم وانغ ،
you don't have to say any more.
لا داعي لقول المزيد.
Maybe I'm the image Miss Su said,
ربما أنا صورة قالت السيدة سو ،
so let's go back.
لذا دعنا نعود.
Go back and pack up.
عد وحزم أمتعتهم.
Moving out of the old house,
الخروج من المنزل القديم ،
I was thinking,
كنت افكر،
Maybe my father
ربما والدي
was right.
كان صحيحا.
Sir,
سيد،
there must be a misunderstanding.
يجب أن يكون هناك سوء فهم.